<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' standalone='yes' ?>
<map>
    <int name="mosh-client:version" value="116" />
    <boolean name="g25_i" value="true" />
    <string name="account_hash">19a093afcee2a1df8bb6ac14d79843</string>
    <string name="19a093afcee2a1df8bb6ac14d79843">NL7nZx31y2o=#4M6tlacFz3RtJitwuBvFhw==#iiWfQ8rydpCV4PA/UyJxbHnunQmQin8td4G6suJK5og=</string>
    <int name="telnet:version" value="116" />
    <string name="bookclub_list">[{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Luciano Ramalho&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1491946008&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51R8PdjjOnL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Python\u2019s simplicity lets you become productive quickly, but this often means you aren\u2019t using everything it has to offer.  With this hands-on guide, you\u2019ll learn how to write effective, idiomatic Python code by leveraging its best\u2014and possibly most neglected\u2014features. Author Luciano Ramalho takes you through Python\u2019s core language features and libraries, and shows you how to make your code shorter, faster, and more readable at the same time.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many experienced programmers try to bend Python to fit patterns they learned from other languages, and never discover Python features outside of their experience. With this book, those Python programmers will thoroughly learn how to become proficient in Python 3.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This book covers:&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Python data model:&lt;\/b&gt; understand how special methods are the key to the consistent behavior of objects&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Data structures:&lt;\/b&gt; take full advantage of built-in types, and understand the text vs bytes duality in the Unicode age&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Functions as objects:&lt;\/b&gt; view Python functions as first-class objects, and understand how this affects popular design patterns&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Object-oriented idioms:&lt;\/b&gt; build classes by learning about references, mutability, interfaces, operator overloading, and multiple inheritance&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Control flow:&lt;\/b&gt; leverage context managers, generators, coroutines, and concurrency with the concurrent.futures and asyncio packages&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Metaprogramming:&lt;\/b&gt; understand how properties, attribute descriptors, class decorators, and metaclasses work&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;&lt;\/div&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1454513549611,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1491946008&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;206eb8b8-664c-421c-b039-ce898b601b36&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Fluent Python&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1491946008/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Jeff Geerling&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;098639341X&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/514UzpZxhHL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;Covers Ansible 2.0! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ansible is a simple, but powerful, server and configuration management tool (with a few other tricks up its sleeve). This book helps those familiar with the command line and basic shell scripting start using Ansible to provision and manage anywhere from one to thousands of servers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The book begins with fundamentals, like installing Ansible, setting up a basic inventory file, and basic concepts, then guides you through Ansible's many uses, including ad-hoc commands, basic and advanced playbooks, application deployments, multiple-provider server provisioning, and even Docker orchestration! Everything is explained with pertinent real-world examples, often using Vagrant-managed virtual machines.&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1450289591868,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;098639341X&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;2ee70299-bc4a-45a5-9925-2fc0d6fac720&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Ansible for DevOps: Server and configuration management for humans&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/098639341X/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Ben Clark&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1494295504&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/31QXtYn4UiL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;The Red Team Field Manual (RTFM) is a no fluff, but thorough reference guide for serious Red Team members who routinely find themselves on a mission without Google or the time to scan through a man page. The RTFM contains the basic syntax for commonly used Linux and Windows command line tools, but it also encapsulates unique use cases for powerful tools such as Python and Windows PowerShell. The RTFM will repeatedly save you time looking up the hard to remember Windows nuances such as Windows wmic and dsquery command line tools, key registry values, scheduled tasks syntax, startup locations and Windows scripting. More importantly, it should teach you some new red team techniques.&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1450289602381,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1494295504&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;32580eb9-407f-416f-856b-d200a7c7e98b&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Rtfm: Red Team Field Manual&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1494295504/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Gene Kim&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;0988262509&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51cc0AxcINL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bill is an IT manager at Parts Unlimited. It's Tuesday morning and on his drive into the office, Bill gets a call from the CEO. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The company's new IT initiative, code named Phoenix Project, is critical to the future of Parts Unlimited, but the project is massively over budget and very late. The CEO wants Bill to report directly to him and fix the mess in ninety days or else Bill's entire department will be outsourced. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With the help of a prospective board member and his mysterious philosophy of The Three Ways, Bill starts to see that IT work has more in common with manufacturing plant work than he ever imagined. With the clock ticking, Bill must organize work flow streamline interdepartmental communications, and effectively serve the other business functions at Parts Unlimited. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In a fast-paced and entertaining style, three luminaries of the DevOps movement deliver a story that anyone who works in IT will recognize. Readers will not only learn how to improve their own IT organizations, they'll never view IT the same way again.&lt;\/span&gt;&lt;\/span&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1449864902423,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;0988262509&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;5f97c3f2-2b33-4481-a40b-148b74895a4b&quot;,&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0988262509/?tag=juicessh-21&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;The Phoenix Project: A Novel about IT, DevOps, and Helping Your Business Win&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0988262509/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;chromatic&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1680500880&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/41-3QvOby5L._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;p&gt;A Perl expert can solve a problem in a few lines of well-tested code. Now you can unlock these powers for yourself. &lt;i&gt;Modern Perl&lt;\/i&gt; teaches you how Perl really works. It's the only book that explains Perl thoroughly, from its philosophical roots to the pragmatic decisions that help you solve real problems--and keep them solved. You'll understand how the language fits together and discover the secrets used by the global Perl community. This beloved guide is now completely updated for Perl 5.22.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;When you have to solve a problem now, reach for Perl. When you have to solve a problem right, reach for &lt;i&gt;Modern Perl&lt;\/i&gt;. Discover how to scale your skills from one-liners to asynchronous Unicode-aware web services and everything in between.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;Modern Perl&lt;\/i&gt; will take you from novice to proficient Perl hacker. You'll see which features of modern Perl will make you more productive, and which features of this well-loved language are best left in the past. Along the way, you'll take advantage of Perl to write well-tested, clear, maintainable code that evolves with you. Learn how the language works, how to take advantage of the CPAN's immense trove of time-tested solutions, and how to write clear, concise, powerful code that runs everywhere. Specific coverage explains how to use Moose, how to write testable code, and how to deploy and maintain real-world Perl applications.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This new edition covers the new features of Perl 5.20 and Perl 5.22, including all the new operators, standard library changes, bug and security fixes, and productivity enhancements. It gives you what you need to use the most up-to-date Perl most effectively, all day, every day.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;What You Need:&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Perl 5.16 or newer (Perl 5.20 or 5.22 preferred). Installation/upgrade instructions included.&lt;\/p&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1451070764022,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1680500880&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;572a31b7-2f8d-4b9c-816d-aa79dee517b0&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Modern Perl&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1680500880/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Evi Nemeth&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;0131480057&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/61%2B57ajucML._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;BLOCKQUOTE&gt;  &lt;P style=\&quot;MARGIN: 0px\&quot;&gt; &lt;I&gt;\u201cAs an author, editor, and publisher, I never paid much attention to the competition\u2013except in a few cases. This is one of those cases. The UNIX System Administration Handbook is one of the few books we ever measured ourselves against.\u201d    &lt;\/I&gt; &lt;\/P&gt;  &lt;P style=\&quot;MARGIN: 0px\&quot;&gt;\u2013From the Foreword by Tim O\u2019Reilly, founder of O\u2019Reilly Media&lt;\/P&gt;  &lt;P style=\&quot;MARGIN: 0px\&quot;&gt; &lt;\/P&gt;  &lt;P style=\&quot;MARGIN: 0px\&quot;&gt; &lt;I&gt;\u201cThis book is fun and functional as a desktop reference. If you use UNIX and Linux systems, you need this book in your short-reach library. It covers a bit of the systems\u2019 history but doesn\u2019t bloviate. It\u2019s just straightfoward information delivered in colorful and memorable fashion.\u201d&lt;\/I&gt;   &lt;\/P&gt;  &lt;P style=\&quot;MARGIN: 0px\&quot;&gt;\u2013Jason A. Nunnelley&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; &lt;I&gt;\u201cThis is a comprehensive guide to the care and feeding of UNIX and Linux systems. The authors present the facts along with seasoned advice and real-world examples. Their perspective on the variations among systems is valuable for anyone who runs a heterogeneous computing facility.\u201d   &lt;\/I&gt; &lt;\/P&gt;  &lt;P style=\&quot;MARGIN: 0px\&quot;&gt;\u2013Pat Parseghian&lt;\/P&gt; &lt;\/BLOCKQUOTE&gt;  &lt;P style=\&quot;MARGIN: 0px\&quot;&gt;The twentieth anniversary edition of the world\u2019s best-selling UNIX system administration book has been made even better by adding coverage of the leading Linux distributions: Ubuntu, openSUSE, and RHEL.  &lt;\/P&gt;  &lt;P style=\&quot;MARGIN: 0px\&quot;&gt; &lt;\/P&gt;  &lt;P style=\&quot;MARGIN: 0px\&quot;&gt;This book approaches system administration in a practical way and is an invaluable reference for both new administrators and experienced professionals. It details best practices for every facet of system administration, including storage management, network design and administration, email, web hosting, scripting, software configuration management, performance analysis, Windows interoperability, virtualization, DNS, security, management of IT service organizations, and much more. &lt;B&gt; &lt;I&gt; &lt;B&gt;UNIX® and Linux® System Administration Handbook, Fourth Edition, &lt;\/B&gt; &lt;\/I&gt; &lt;\/B&gt;reflects the current versions of these operating systems:&lt;\/P&gt;  &lt;BLOCKQUOTE&gt;  &lt;P style=\&quot;MARGIN: 0px\&quot;&gt;Ubuntu® Linux&lt;BR&gt;openSUSE® Linux&lt;BR&gt;Red Hat® Enterprise Linux®&lt;BR&gt;Oracle America® Solaris™ (&lt;I&gt;formerly Sun Solaris&lt;\/I&gt;)&lt;BR&gt;HP HP-UX®&lt;BR&gt;IBM AIX®&lt;\/P&gt; &lt;\/BLOCKQUOTE&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1449864918894,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;0131480057&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;b07fcce9-0160-4adc-b8ac-5e5bb6de1a10&quot;,&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0131480057/?tag=juicessh-21&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;UNIX and Linux System Administration Handbook, 4th Edition&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0131480057/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Michael W Lucas&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1470069717&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51WNSd78ZKL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;span&gt;Secure Shell (SSH) lets systems administrators securely manage remote systems. But most people only use the bare minimum SSH offers. Used properly, SSH simplifies your job and improves security.&lt;\/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;This book saves you from sifting a decade of obsolete online tutorials and quickly gets you running:SSH with the OpenSSH server and the PuTTY and OpenSSH clients. You will:&lt;\/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Eliminate passwords.&lt;\/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Manage access to your SSH server by users, groups, addresses, and more&lt;\/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Securely move files around your network&lt;\/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Forward graphic displays from one host to another&lt;\/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Forward TCP/IP connections &lt;\/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Centrally manage host keys and client configurations&lt;\/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Use SSH as a secure transport for other applications&lt;\/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Secure applications run over SSH&lt;\/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Build Virtual Private Networks with OpenSSH&lt;\/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;And more! This book quickly and painlessly simplifies life for anyone using SSH.&lt;\/span&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1452390373299,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1470069717&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;b1289a08-070a-45f2-9827-70d77fcea0d4&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;SSH Mastery: OpenSSH, PuTTY, Tunnels and Keys&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1470069717/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Sam Newman&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1491950358&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51gi3fUMdzL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distributed systems have become more fine-grained in the past 10 years, shifting from code-heavy monolithic applications to smaller, self-contained microservices. But developing these systems brings its own set of headaches. With lots of examples and practical advice, this book takes a holistic view of the topics that system architects and administrators must consider when building, managing, and evolving microservice architectures.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microservice technologies are moving quickly. Author Sam Newman provides you with a firm grounding in the concepts while diving into current solutions for modeling, integrating, testing, deploying, and monitoring your own autonomous services. You\u2019ll follow a fictional company throughout the book to learn how building a microservice architecture affects a single domain.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Discover how microservices allow you to align your system design with your organization\u2019s goals&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Learn options for integrating a service with the rest of your system&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Take an incremental approach when splitting monolithic codebases&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deploy individual microservices through continuous integration&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Examine the complexities of testing and monitoring distributed services&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage security with user-to-service and service-to-service models&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understand the challenges of scaling microservice architectures&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;&lt;\/div&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1450132011889,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1491950358&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;b42c7e0d-dda8-400e-be8c-6601b77b9e26&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Building Microservices&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1491950358/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Thomas A. Limoncelli&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;0596007833&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51n9asjUhiL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time is a precious commodity, especially if you're a system administrator. No other job pulls people in so many directions at once.  Users interrupt you constantly with requests, preventing you from getting anything done.  Your managers want you to get long-term projects done but flood you with requests for quick-fixes that prevent you from ever getting to those long-term projects. But the pressure is on you to produce and it only increases with time. What do you do?&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The answer is time management. And not just any time management theory--you want &lt;i&gt;Time Management for System Administrators&lt;\/i&gt;, to be exact. With keen insights into the challenges you face as a sys admin, bestselling author Thomas Limoncelli has put together a collection of tips and techniques that will help you cultivate the time management skills you need to flourish as a system administrator.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Time Management for System Administrators&lt;\/i&gt; understands that an Sys Admin often has competing goals: the concurrent responsibilities of working on large projects and taking care of a user's needs.  That's why it focuses on strategies that help you work through daily tasks, yet still allow you to handle critical situations that inevitably arise.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among other skills, you'll learn how to:&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage interruptions&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eliminate timewasters&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep an effective calendar&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop routines for things that occur regularly&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use your brain only for what you're currently working on&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prioritize based on customer expectations&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Document and automate processes for faster execution&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, the book doesn't confine itself to just the work environment, either.  It also offers tips on how to apply these time management tools to your social life.  It's the first step to a more productive, happier you.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;\/div&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1449864918894,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;0596007833&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;d03f6e21-e848-4a5d-aa04-3eaf0b2e6353&quot;,&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0596007833/?tag=juicessh-21&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Time Management for System Administrators&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0596007833/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Christopher Negus&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1118999878&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51HVZXbAxfL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;b&gt;The industry favorite Linux guide, updated for Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7 and the cloud&lt;\/b&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Linux Bible, 9th Edition&lt;\/i&gt; is the ultimate hands-on Linux user guide, whether you're a true beginner or a more advanced user navigating recent changes. This updated ninth edition covers the latest versions of Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7 (RHEL 7), Fedora 21, and Ubuntu 14.04 LTS, and includes new information on cloud computing and development with guidance on Openstack and Cloudforms. With a focus on RHEL 7, this practical guide gets you up to speed quickly on the new enhancements for enterprise-quality file systems, the new boot process and services management, firewalld, and the GNOME 3 desktop. Written by a Red Hat expert, this book provides the clear explanations and step-by-step instructions that demystify Linux and bring the new features seamlessly into your workflow.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This useful guide assumes a base of little or no Linux knowledge, and takes you step by step through what you need to know to get the job done.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Get Linux up and running quickly&lt;\/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Master basic operations and tackle more advanced tasks&lt;\/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Get up to date on the recent changes to Linux server system management&lt;\/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bring Linux to the cloud using Openstack and Cloudforms&lt;\/li&gt; &lt;\/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Linux Bible, 9th Edition&lt;\/i&gt; is the one resource you need, and provides the hands-on training that gets you on track in a flash.&lt;\/p&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1451070764022,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1118999878&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;d0ffefcc-7454-45f7-8263-015d2306427c&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Linux Bible&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1118999878/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;James Turnbull&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1590599780&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51yuULB3heL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;p&gt;Competent system administrators know their success hinges upon being able to perform often tedious tasks with rigor and punctuality. Such metrics are often achieved only by instituting a considerable degree of automation, something that has become even more crucial as IT environments continue to scale both in terms of size and complexity. One of the most powerful system administration tools to be released is Puppet, a solution capable of automating nearly every aspect of a system administrator's job, from user management, to software installation, to even configuring server services such as FTP and LDAP.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pulling Strings with Puppet: Configuration Management Made Easy&lt;\/em&gt; is the first book to introduce the powerful Puppet system administration tool. Author &lt;strong&gt;James Turnbull&lt;\/strong&gt; will guide you through Puppet's key features, showing you how to install and configure the software, create automated Puppet tasks, known as recipes, and even create reporting solutions and extend Puppet further to your own needs. A bonus chapter is included covering the Facter library, which makes it a breeze to automate the retrieval of server configuration details such as IP and MAC addresses.&lt;\/p&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1449864918894,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1590599780&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;e31afbc0-bdc9-43b5-92a9-0c1c219588cf&quot;,&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1590599780/?tag=juicessh-21&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Pulling Strings with Puppet: Configuration Management Made Easy (FirstPress)&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1590599780/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;William E. Shotts Jr.&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1593273894&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/517eBAhF%2B8L._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;You've experienced the shiny, point-and-click surface of your Linux computer\u2014now dive below and explore its depths with the power of the command line.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Linux Command Line&lt;\/i&gt; takes you from your very first terminal keystrokes to writing full programs in Bash, the most popular Linux shell. Along the way you'll learn the timeless skills handed down by generations of gray-bearded, mouse-shunning gurus: file navigation, environment configuration, command chaining, pattern matching with regular expressions, and more.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In addition to that practical knowledge, author William Shotts reveals the philosophy behind these tools and the rich heritage that your desktop Linux machine has inherited from Unix supercomputers of yore.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As you make your way through the book's short, easily-digestible chapters, you'll learn how to:&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create and delete files, directories, and symlinks&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Administer your system, including networking, package installation, and process management&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use standard input and output, redirection, and pipelines&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Edit files with Vi, the world's most popular text editor&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Write shell scripts to automate common or boring tasks&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slice and dice text files with cut, paste, grep, patch, and sed&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Once you overcome your initial \&quot;shell shock,\&quot; you'll find that the command line is a natural and expressive way to communicate with your computer. Just don't be surprised if your mouse starts to gather dust.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;\/div&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1458829170021,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1593273894&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;9459c729-d755-4aea-a4cf-43525cf19577&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;The Linux Command Line: A Complete Introduction&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1593273894/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Richard Blum&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;111898384X&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51y%2BYGNnKsL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;Talk directly to your system for a faster workflow with automation capability &lt;p&gt;\&quot;Linux Command Line and Shell Scripting Bible\&quot; is your essential Linux guide. With detailed instruction and abundant examples, this book teaches you how to bypass the graphical interface and communicate directly with your computer, saving time and expanding capability. This third edition incorporates thirty pages of new functional examples that are fully updated to align with the latest Linux features. Beginning with command line fundamentals, the book moves into shell scripting and shows you the practical application of commands in automating frequently performed functions. This guide includes useful tutorials, and a desk reference value of numerous examples. &lt;p&gt;The Linux command line allows you to type specific shell commands directly into the system to manipulate files and query system resources. Command line statements can be combined into short programs called shell scripts, a practice increasing in popularity due to its usefulness in automation. This book is a complete guide providing detailed instruction and expert advice working within this aspect of Linux. Write simple script utilities to automate tasks Understand the shell, and create shell scripts Produce database, e-mail, and web scripts Study scripting examples ranging from basic to advanced &lt;p&gt;Whether used as a tutorial or as a quick reference, this book contains information that every Linux user should know. Why not learn to use the system to its utmost capability? Linux is a robust system with tremendous potential, and \&quot;Linux Command Line and Shell Scripting Bible\&quot; opens the door to new possibilities.&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1460039370586,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;111898384X&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;3e687aac-db6c-46fb-96f0-50fc9f68fffc&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Linux Command Line and Shell Scripting Bible&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/111898384X/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Karl Matthias&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1491917571&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51%2BL3N5XimL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Updated to cover Docker version 1.10&lt;\/strong&gt;&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Docker is quickly changing the way that organizations are deploying software at scale. But understanding how Linux containers fit into your workflow\u2014and getting the integration details right\u2014are not trivial tasks. With this practical guide, you\u2019ll learn how to use Docker to package your applications with all of their dependencies, and then test, ship, scale, and support your containers in production.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two Lead Site Reliability Engineers at New Relic share much of what they have learned from using Docker in production since shortly after its initial release. Their goal is to help you reap the benefits of this technology while avoiding the many setbacks they experienced.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Learn how Docker simplifies dependency management and deployment workflow for your applications&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Start working with Docker images, containers, and command line tools&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use practical techniques to deploy and test Docker-based Linux containers in production&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Debug containers by understanding their composition and internal processes&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deploy production containers at scale inside your data center or cloud environment&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Explore advanced Docker topics, including deployment tools, networking, orchestration, security, and configuration&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;&lt;\/div&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1486320802949,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1491917571&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;99e174e1-337c-4412-a911-ab4b46eddde6&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Docker: Up &amp; Running: Shipping Reliable Containers in Production&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1491917571/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Viktor Farcic&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;152391744X&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/41eB4yc15gL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;This book is about different techniques that help us architect software in a better and more efficient way with microservices packed as immutable containers, tested and deployed continuously to servers that are automatically provisioned with configuration management tools. It's about fast, reliable and continuous deployments with zero-downtime and ability to roll-back. It's about scaling to any number of servers, design of self-healing systems capable of recuperation from both hardware and software failures and about centralized logging and monitoring of the cluster.In other words, this book envelops the whole microservices development and deployment lifecycle using some of the latest and greatest practices and tools. We'll use Docker, Kubernetes, Ansible, Ubuntu, Docker Swarm and Docker Compose, Consul, etcd, Registrator, confd, and so on. We'll go through many practices and even more tools. Finally, while there will be a lot of theory, this is a hands-on book. You won't be able to complete it by reading it in a metro on a way to work. You'll have to read this book while in front of the computer and get your hands dirty.&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1486320802949,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;152391744X&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;501379ab-db88-4f49-8c25-6eeca63d3945&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;The DevOps 2.0 Toolkit: Automating the Continuous Deployment Pipeline with Containerized Microservices&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/152391744X/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Jesse Keating&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;178439548X&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/41rsde3tifL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Design, develop, and solve real world automation and orchestration needs by unlocking the automation capabilities of Ansible&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;About This Book&lt;\/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Discover how Ansible works in detail&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Explore use cases for Ansible's advanced features including task delegation, fast failures, and serial task execution&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extend Ansible with custom modules, plugins, and inventory sources&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who This Book Is For&lt;\/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This book is intended for Ansible developers and operators who have an understanding of the core elements and applications but are now looking to enhance their skills in applying automation using Ansible.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What You Will Learn&lt;\/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understand Ansible's code and logic flow&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Safeguard sensitive data within Ansible&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Access and manipulate complex variable data within Ansible playbooks&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Handle task results to manipulate change and failure definitions&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Organize Ansible content into a simple structure&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Craft a multi-tier rollout playbook utilizing load balancers and manipulating your monitoring system&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Utilize advanced Ansible features to orchestrate rolling updates with almost no service disruptions&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot Ansible failures to understand and resolve issues&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extend Ansible with custom modules, plugins, or inventory sources&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;In Detail&lt;\/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Automation is critical to success in the world of DevOps. How quickly and efficiently an application deployment can be automated, or a new infrastructure can be built up, can be the difference between a successful product or a failure. Ansible provides a simple yet powerful automation engine. Beyond the basics of Ansible lie a host of advanced features which are available to help you increase efficiency and accomplish complex orchestrations with ease.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This book provides you with the knowledge you need to understand how Ansible works at a fundamental level and leverage its advanced capabilities. You'll learn how to encrypt Ansible content at rest and decrypt data at runtime. You will master the advanced features and capabilities required to tackle the complex automation challenges of today and beyond. You will gain detailed knowledge of Ansible workflows, explore use cases for advanced features, craft well thought out orchestrations, troubleshoot unexpected behaviour, and extend Ansible through customizations. Finally, you will discover the methods used to examine and debug Ansible operations, helping you to understand and resolve issues.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Style and approach&lt;\/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A clear, practical guide that covers best practise, system architecture and design aspects that will help you master Ansible with ease.&lt;\/p&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1486320802949,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;178439548X&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;fc6b02b5-9f36-4ff7-8409-242212971c15&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Mastering Ansible&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/178439548X/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Kief Morris&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1491924357&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51l2xDf6sLL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Virtualization, cloud, containers, server automation, and software-defined networking are meant to simplify IT operations. But many organizations adopting these technologies have found that it only leads to a faster-growing sprawl of unmanageable systems. This is where infrastructure as code can help. With this practical guide, author Kief Morris of ThoughtWorks shows you how to effectively use principles, practices, and patterns pioneered through the DevOps movement to manage cloud age infrastructure.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ideal for system administrators, infrastructure engineers, team leads, and architects, this book demonstrates various tools, techniques, and patterns you can use to implement infrastructure as code. In three parts, you\u2019ll learn about the platforms and tooling involved in creating and configuring infrastructure elements, patterns for using these tools, and practices for making infrastructure as code work in your environment.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Examine the pitfalls that organizations fall into when adopting the new generation of infrastructure technologies&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understand the capabilities and service models of dynamic infrastructure platforms&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Learn about tools that provide, provision, and configure core infrastructure resources&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Explore services and tools for managing a dynamic infrastructure&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Learn specific patterns and practices for provisioning servers, building server templates, and updating running servers&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;&lt;\/div&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1486320802949,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1491924357&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;cedc4ffa-e0f9-4e77-b06e-86023347aed3&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Infrastructure as Code: Managing Servers in the Cloud&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1491924357/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Jeff Nickoloff&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1633430235&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/518L63vGMpL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Summary&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Docker in Action&lt;\/i&gt; teaches readers how to create, deploy, and manage applications hosted in Docker containers.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Purchase of the print book includes a free eBook in PDF, Kindle, and ePub formats from Manning Publications.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Technology&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea behind Docker is simple. Create a tiny virtual environment, called a container, that holds just your application and its dependencies. The Docker engine uses the host operating system to build and account for these containers. They are easy to install, manage, and remove. Applications running inside containers share resources, making their footprints small.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Book&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Docker in Action&lt;\/i&gt; teaches readers how to create, deploy, and manage applications hosted in Docker containers. After starting with a clear explanation of the Docker model, you will learn how to package applications in containers, including techniques for testing and distributing applications. You will also learn how to run programs securely and how to manage shared resources. Using carefully designed examples, the book teaches you how to orchestrate containers and applications from installation to removal. Along the way, you'll discover techniques for using Docker on systems ranging from dev-and-test machines to full-scale cloud deployments.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What's Inside&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;li&gt;Packaging containers for deployment&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Installing, managing, and removing containers&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working with Docker images&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Distributing with DockerHub&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Reader&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Readers need only have a working knowledge of the Linux OS. No prior knowledge of Docker is assumed.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Author&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jeff Nickoloff&lt;\/b&gt;, a software engineer, has presented Docker and its applications to hundreds of developers and administrators at Desert Code Camp, Amazon.com, and technology meetups.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Table of Contents&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;PART 1   KEEPING A TIDY COMPUTER&lt;\/h4&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Welcome to Docker&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Running software in containers&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Software installation simplified&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Persistent storage and shared state with volumes&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Network exposure&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Limiting risk with isolation&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;h4&gt;PART 2   PACKAGING SOFTWARE FOR DISTRIBUTION&lt;\/h4&gt;&lt;li&gt;Packaging software in images&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build automation and advanced image considerations&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Public and private software distribution&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Running customized registries&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;h4&gt;PART 3   MULTI-CONTAINER AND MULTI-HOST ENVIRONMENTS&lt;\/h4&gt;&lt;li&gt;Declarative environments with Docker&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clusters with Machine and Swarm&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ol&gt;&lt;\/div&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1486320802949,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1633430235&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;4d2bb720-7ac9-44db-a504-4a9b6a43b993&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Docker in Action&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1633430235/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Jennifer Davis&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1491926309&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51mCVngDT6L._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some companies think that adopting devops means bringing in specialists or a host of new tools. With this practical guide, you\u2019ll learn why devops is a professional and cultural movement that calls for change from &lt;i&gt;inside&lt;\/i&gt; your organization. Authors Katherine Daniels and Jennifer Davis provide several approaches for improving collaboration within teams, creating affinity among teams, promoting efficient tool usage in your company, and scaling up what works throughout your organization\u2019s inflection points.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Devops stresses iterative efforts to break down information silos, monitor relationships, and repair misunderstandings that arise between and within teams in your organization. By applying the actionable strategies in this book, you can make sustainable changes in your environment regardless of your level within your organization.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Explore the foundations of devops and learn the four pillars of effective devops&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Encourage collaboration to help individuals work together and build durable and long-lasting relationships&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create affinity among teams while balancing differing goals or metrics&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Accelerate cultural direction by selecting tools and workflows that complement your organization&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot common problems and misunderstandings that can arise throughout the organizational lifecycle&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Learn from case studies from organizations and individuals to help inform your own devops journey&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;&lt;\/div&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1486320802949,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1491926309&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;e7511be0-fa42-413e-9bef-820802f24fde&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Effective DevOps: Building a Culture of Collaboration, Affinity, and Tooling at Scale&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1491926309/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Andreas Wittig&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1617292885&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51imZSASpPL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Summary&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Amazon Web Services in Action&lt;\/i&gt; introduces you to computing, storing, and networking in the AWS cloud. The book will teach you about the most important services on AWS. You will also learn about best practices regarding automation, security, high availability, and scalability.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Purchase of the print book includes a free eBook in PDF, Kindle, and ePub formats from Manning Publications.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Technology&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Physical data centers require lots of equipment and take time and resources to manage. If you need a data center, but don't want to build your own, Amazon Web Services may be your solution. Whether you're analyzing real-time data, building software as a service, or running an e-commerce site, AWS offers you a reliable cloud-based platform with services that scale. All services are controllable via an API which allows you to automate your infrastructure.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Book&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Amazon Web Services in Action&lt;\/i&gt; introduces you to computing, storing, and networking in the AWS cloud. The book will teach you about the most important services on AWS. You will also learn about best practices regarding security, high availability and scalability.You'll start with a broad overview of cloud computing and AWS and learn how to spin-up servers manually and from the command line. You'll learn how to automate your infrastructure by programmatically calling the AWS API to control every part of AWS. You will be introduced to the concept of Infrastructure as Code with the help of AWS CloudFormation.You will learn about different approaches to deploy applications on AWS. You'll also learn how to secure your infrastructure by isolating networks, controlling traffic and managing access to AWS resources. Next, you'll learn options and techniques for storing your data. You will experience how to integrate AWS services into your own applications by the use of SDKs. Finally, this book teaches you how to design for high availability, fault tolerance, and scalability.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What's Inside&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Overview of cloud concepts and patterns&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage servers on EC2 for cost-effectiveness&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Infrastructure automation with Infrastructure as Code (AWS CloudFormation)&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deploy applications on AWS&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Store data on AWS: SQL, NoSQL, object storage and block storage&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Integrate Amazon's pre-built services&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Architect highly available and fault tolerant systems&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Reader&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Written for developers and DevOps engineers moving distributed applications to the AWS platform.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Authors&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Andreas Wittig&lt;\/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Michael Wittig&lt;\/b&gt; are software engineers and consultants focused on AWS and web development.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Table of Contents&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;h5&gt;PART 1  GETTING STARTED&lt;\/h5&gt;&lt;li&gt;What is Amazon Web Services?&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A simple example: WordPress in five minutes&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;h5&gt;PART 2  BUILDING VIRTUAL INFRASTRUCTURE WITH SERVERS AND NETWORKING&lt;\/h5&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using virtual servers: EC2&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Programming your infrastructure: the command line, SDKs, and CloudFormation&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Automating deployment: CloudFormation, Elastic Beanstalk, and OpsWorks&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Securing your system: IAM, security groups, and VPC&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;h5&gt;PART 3  STORING DATA IN THE CLOUD&lt;\/h5&gt;&lt;li&gt;Storing your objects: S3 and Glacier&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Storing your data on hard drives: EBS and instance store&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using a relational database service: RDS&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Programming for the NoSQL database service: DynamoDB&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;h5&gt;PART 4  ARCHITECTING ON AWS&lt;\/h5&gt;&lt;li&gt;Achieving high availability: availability zones, auto-scaling, and CloudWatch&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Decoupling your infrastructure: ELB and SQS&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Designing for fault-tolerance&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scaling up and down: auto-scaling and CloudWatch&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ol&gt;&lt;\/div&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1486320802949,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1617292885&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;5d2a8d70-a02f-48d6-9cb8-e5a6df281538&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Amazon Web Services in Action&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1617292885/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;David Beazley&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1449340377&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51hFtDvqgfL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you need help writing programs in Python 3, or want to update older Python 2 code, this book is just the ticket. Packed with practical recipes written and tested with Python 3.3, this unique cookbook is for experienced Python programmers who want to focus on modern tools and idioms.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inside, you\u2019ll find complete recipes for more than a dozen topics, covering the core Python language as well as tasks common to a wide variety of application domains. Each recipe contains code samples you can use in your projects right away, along with a discussion about how and why the solution works.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Topics include:&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Data Structures and Algorithms&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strings and Text&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Numbers, Dates, and Times&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Iterators and Generators&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Files and I/O&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Data Encoding and Processing&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Functions&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Classes and Objects&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Metaprogramming&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Modules and Packages&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Network and Web Programming&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Concurrency&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Utility Scripting and System Administration&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Testing, Debugging, and Exceptions&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;C Extensions&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;&lt;\/div&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1486320802949,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1449340377&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;adebb540-5640-4d07-803c-43af92c2b894&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Python Cookbook, Third edition&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1449340377/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Brett Slatkin&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;0134034287&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51G2L3Ghp5L._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;It's easy to start writing code with Python: that's why the language is so immensely popular. However, Python has unique strengths, charms, and expressivity that can be hard to grasp at first -- as well as hidden pitfalls that can easily trip you up if you aren't aware of them. &lt;b&gt;Effective Python&lt;\/b&gt; will help you harness the full power of Python to write exceptionally robust, efficient, maintainable, and well-performing code. Utilizing the concise, scenario-driven style pioneered in Scott Meyers's best-selling &lt;i&gt;Effective C++&lt;\/i&gt;, Brett Slatkin brings together 59 Python best practices, tips, shortcuts, and realistic code examples from expert programmers.&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;Through realistic examples, Slatkin uncovers little-known Python quirks, intricacies, and idioms that powerfully impact code behavior and performance. You'll learn how to choose the most efficient and effective way to accomplish key tasks when multiple options exist, and how to write code that's easier to understand, maintain, and improve.&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;Drawing on his deep understanding of Python's capabilities, Slatkin offers practical advice for each major area of development with both Python 3.x and Python 2.x. Coverage includes:&lt;br&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Algorithms&lt;\/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Objects&lt;\/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Concurrency&lt;\/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Collaboration&lt;\/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Built-in modules&lt;\/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Production techniques&lt;\/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;And more&lt;\/li&gt; &lt;\/ul&gt;  Each section contains specific, actionable guidelines organized into items, each with carefully worded advice supported by detailed technical arguments and illuminating examples. Using &lt;b&gt;Effective Python&lt;\/b&gt;, you can systematically improve all the Python code you write: not by blindly following rules or mimicking incomprehensible idioms, but by gaining a deep understanding of the technical reasons why they make sense.&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1486320802949,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;0134034287&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;fd1c551d-e5c4-4f71-b503-8b78e65d70ea&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Effective Python: 59 Specific Ways to Write Better Python (Effective Software Development Series)&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0134034287/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Jake VanderPlas&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1491912057&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/5125td-xIkL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Python Data Science Handbook provides a reference to the breadth of computational and statistical methods that are central to data-intensive science, research, and discovery. People with a programming background who want to use Python effectively for data science tasks will learn how to face a variety of problems: e.g., how can I read this data format into my script? How can I manipulate, transform, and clean this data? How can I visualize this type of data? How can I use this data to gain insight, answer questions, or to build statistical or machine learning models?&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This book is a reference for day-to-day Python-enabled data science, covering both the computational and statistical skills necessary to effectively work with . The discussion is augmented with frequent example applications, showing how the wide breadth of open source Python tools can be used together to analyze, manipulate, visualize, and learn from data.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;\/div&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1486320802949,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1491912057&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;2622b4a9-3694-44e0-a459-1143825dc1d5&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Python Data Science Handbook: Essential Tools for Working with Data&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1491912057/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Sebastian Raschka&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1783555130&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51a%2B9LUynLL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unlock deeper insights into Machine Leaning with this vital guide to cutting-edge predictive analytics&lt;\/b&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;About This Book&lt;\/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leverage Python's most powerful open-source libraries for deep learning, data wrangling, and data visualization&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Learn effective strategies and best practices to improve and optimize machine learning systems and algorithms&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ask \u2013 and answer \u2013 tough questions of your data with robust statistical models, built for a range of datasets&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who This Book Is For&lt;\/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you want to find out how to use Python to start answering critical questions of your data, pick up Python Machine Learning \u2013 whether you want to get started from scratch or want to extend your data science knowledge, this is an essential and unmissable resource.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What You Will Learn&lt;\/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Explore how to use different machine learning models to ask different questions of your data&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Learn how to build neural networks using Pylearn 2 and Theano&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Find out how to write clean and elegant Python code that will optimize the strength of your algorithms&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Discover how to embed your machine learning model in a web application for increased accessibility&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Predict continuous target outcomes using regression analysis&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncover hidden patterns and structures in data with clustering&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Organize data using effective pre-processing techniques&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Get to grips with sentiment analysis to delve deeper into textual and social media data&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;In Detail&lt;\/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Machine learning and predictive analytics are transforming the way businesses and other organizations operate. Being able to understand trends and patterns in complex data is critical to success, becoming one of the key strategies for unlocking growth in a challenging contemporary marketplace. Python can help you deliver key insights into your data \u2013 its unique capabilities as a language let you build sophisticated algorithms and statistical models that can reveal new perspectives and answer key questions that are vital for success.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Python Machine Learning gives you access to the world of predictive analytics and demonstrates why Python is one of the world's leading data science languages. If you want to ask better questions of data, or need to improve and extend the capabilities of your machine learning systems, this practical data science book is invaluable. Covering a wide range of powerful Python libraries, including scikit-learn, Theano, and Pylearn2, and featuring guidance and tips on everything from sentiment analysis to neural networks, you'll soon be able to answer some of the most important questions facing you and your organization.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Style and approach&lt;\/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Python Machine Learning connects the fundamental theoretical principles behind machine learning to their practical application in a way that focuses you on asking and answering the right questions. It walks you through the key elements of Python and its powerful machine learning libraries, while demonstrating how to get to grips with a range of statistical models.&lt;\/p&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1486320802949,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1783555130&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;a8e22960-dbd5-430f-b39f-c6f59e4c812f&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Python Machine Learning&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1783555130/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Daniel J. Barrett&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1491927577&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51AbKrNDvaL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you use Linux in your day-to-day work, this popular pocket guide is the perfect on-the-job reference. The third edition features new commands for processing image files and audio files, running and killing programs, reading and modifying the system clipboard, and manipulating PDF files, as well as other commands requested by readers. You\u2019ll also find powerful command-line idioms you might not be familiar with, such as process substitution and piping into bash.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Linux Pocket Guide&lt;\/i&gt; provides an organized learning path to help you gain mastery of the most useful and important commands. Whether you\u2019re a novice who needs to get up to speed on Linux or an experienced user who wants a concise and functional reference, this guide provides quick answers.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selected topics include:&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The filesystem and shell&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;File creation and editing&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Text manipulation and pipelines&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Backups and remote storage&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Viewing and controlling processes&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;User account management&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Becoming the superuser&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Network connections&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Audio and video&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Installing software&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Programming with shell scripts&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;&lt;\/div&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1486320802949,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1491927577&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;5067c58d-78c0-4f0b-980c-80419c58db2c&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Linux Pocket Guide: Essential Commands&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1491927577/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Jaosn Cannon&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;151738043X&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/41zTJXtmGZL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;h1&gt;Shell Scripting Made Easy&lt;\/h1&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you want to learn how to write shell scripts like a pro, solve real-world problems, or automate repetitive and complex tasks, read on.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hello. My name is Jason Cannon and I'm the author of &lt;i&gt;Linux for Beginners&lt;\/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Python Programming for Beginners&lt;\/i&gt;, and an instructor to thousands of satisfied students. I started my IT career in the late 1990's as a Unix and Linux System Engineer and I'll be sharing my real-world shell scripting and bash programming experience with you throughout this book.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;By the end of this book you will be able to create shell scripts with ease. You'll learn how to take tedious and repetitive tasks and turn them into programs that will save you time and simplify your life on Linux, Unix, or MAC systems.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Here is what you will get and learn by reading this &lt;i&gt;Shell Scripting&lt;\/i&gt; book:&lt;\/h2&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;A step-by-step process of writing shell scripts that solve real-world problems.&lt;\/li&gt;     &lt;li&gt;The #1 thing you must do every time you create a shell script.&lt;\/li&gt;     &lt;li&gt;How to quickly find and fix the most shell scripting errors.&lt;\/li&gt;     &lt;li&gt;How to accept input from a user and then make decisions on that input.&lt;\/li&gt;     &lt;li&gt;How to accept and process command line arguments.&lt;\/li&gt;     &lt;li&gt;What special variables are available, how to use them in your shell scripts, and when to do so.&lt;\/li&gt;     &lt;li&gt;A shell script creation check list -- You'll never have to guess what to include in each of your shell scripts again. Just use this simple check list.&lt;\/li&gt;     &lt;li&gt;A shell script template (boilerplate). Use this format for each of your shell scripts. It shows exactly what to include and where everything goes. Eliminate guesswork!&lt;\/li&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Practice exercises with solutions so you can start using what you learn right away.&lt;\/li&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Real-world examples of shell scripts from my personal collection.&lt;\/li&gt;     &lt;li&gt;A download that contains the scripts used in the book and lessons. You'll be able to look at and experiment with everything you're learning.&lt;\/li&gt; &lt;\/ul&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Learn to Program Using Any Shell Scirpting Language&lt;\/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;What you learn in this book can be applied to any shell, however the focus is on the bash shell and you'll learn some really advanced bash features. Again, whether you're using bash, bourne (sh), KornShell (ksh), C shell (csh), Z shell (zsh), or even the tcsh shell, you'll be able to put what you learn in this book to good use.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Perfect for Linux, Unix, Mac and More!&lt;\/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Also, you'll be able to use these scripts on any Linux environment including Ubuntu, Debian, Linux Mint, RedHat, Fedora, OpenSUSE, Slackware, Kali Linux and more. You're scripts will even run on other operating systems such as Apple's Mac OS X, Oracle's Solaris, IBM's AIX, HP's HP-UX, FreeBSD, NetBSD, and OpenBSD.&lt;\/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scroll up, click the Buy Now With 1 Click button and get started learning Linux today!&lt;\/strong&gt;&lt;\/p&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1486320802949,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;151738043X&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;56985da4-ee77-46ce-9019-d766e74cbfdc&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Shell Scripting: How to Automate Command Line Tasks Using Bash Scripting and Shell Programming&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/151738043X/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Dave Taylor&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1593276028&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51g8L%2BdqZhL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shell scripts are an efficient way to interact with your machine and manage your files and system operations. With just a few lines of code, your computer will do exactly what you want it to do. But you can also use shell scripts for many other essential (and not-so-essential) tasks.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This second edition of &lt;i&gt;Wicked Cool Shell Scripts&lt;\/i&gt; offers a collection of useful, customizable, and fun shell scripts for solving common problems and personalizing your computing environment. Each chapter contains ready-to-use scripts and explanations of how they work, why you'd want to use them, and suggestions for changing and expanding them. You'll find a mix of classic favorites, like a disk backup utility that keeps your files safe when your system crashes, a password manager, a weather tracker, and several games, as well as 23 brand-new scripts, including:&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A ZIP code lookup tool that reports the city and state&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A Bitcoin address information retriever&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A suite of tools for working with cloud services like Dropbox and iCloud&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tools for renaming and applying commands to files in bulk&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Image processing and editing tools&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;Whether you want to save time managing your system or just find new ways to goof off, these scripts are wicked cool!&lt;\/div&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1486320802949,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1593276028&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;ea2a5622-ce3f-4d32-aad9-537b7e7c73cf&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Wicked Cool Shell Scripts: 101 Scripts for Linux, OS X, and UNIX Systems&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1593276028/?tag=ju097-20&quot;},{&quot;book&quot;:{&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Kelsey Hightower&quot;,&quot;isbn&quot;:&quot;1491935677&quot;,&quot;__v&quot;:0,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51NpXDNrEyL._SL160_.jpg&quot;,&quot;active&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Legend has it that Google deploys over two billion application containers a week. How\u2019s that possible? Google revealed the secret through a project called Kubernetes, an open source cluster orchestrator (based on its internal Borg system) that radically simplifies the task of building, deploying, and maintaining scalable distributed systems in the cloud. This practical guide shows you how Kubernetes and container technology can help you achieve new levels of velocity, agility, reliability, and efficiency.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Authors Kelsey Hightower, Brendan Burns, and Joe Beda\u2014who\u2019ve worked on Kubernetes at Google and other organizatons\u2014explain how this system fits into the lifecycle of a distributed application. You will learn how to use tools and APIs to automate scalable distributed systems, whether it is for online services, machine-learning applications, or a cluster of Raspberry Pi computers.&lt;\/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Explore the distributed system challenges that Kubernetes addresses&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dive into containerized application development, using containers such as Docker&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create and run containers on Kubernetes, using the docker image format and container runtime&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Explore specialized objects essential for running applications in production&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reliably roll out new software versions without downtime or errors&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Get examples of how to develop and deploy real-world applications in Kubernetes&lt;\/li&gt;&lt;\/ul&gt;&lt;\/div&gt;&quot;,&quot;modified&quot;:1506729443989,&quot;asin&quot;:&quot;1491935677&quot;,&quot;_id&quot;:&quot;6af753ba-3210-4b03-b72c-19d49088749a&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Kubernetes: Up and Running: Dive into the Future of Infrastructure&quot;},&quot;affiliateurl&quot;:&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1491935677/?tag=ju097-20&quot;}]</string>
    <string name="plugins_list">[{&quot;package&quot;:&quot;com.sonelli.juicessh.performancemonitor&quot;,&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Sonelli Ltd&quot;,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;Performance Monitor&quot;,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://api.sonelli.com/images/plugins/com.sonelli.juicessh.performancemonitor.png&quot;,&quot;opensource&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;A visual representation of the CPU, RAM, load average, network and disk utilisation of an SSH server. Currently this plugin will only work with Linux servers, however it is open source so feel free to submit a pull request if you want to add support for another system type.&quot;,&quot;repository&quot;:&quot;https://github.com/Sonelli/juicessh-performancemonitor&quot;,&quot;email&quot;:&quot;support@sonelli.com&quot;,&quot;url&quot;:&quot;http://juicessh.com&quot;},{&quot;package&quot;:&quot;net.yawitz.configreader&quot;,&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Yawitz Tech&quot;,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;OpenSSH Importer&quot;,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://api.sonelli.com/images/plugins/com.yawitz.configreader.png&quot;,&quot;opensource&quot;:&quot;false&quot;,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;Imports connections from an ssh_config file into JuiceSSH.&quot;,&quot;repository&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;email&quot;:&quot;elibyy@gmail.com&quot;,&quot;url&quot;:&quot;n/a&quot;},{&quot;package&quot;:&quot;com.groupsecs.juicesshclustersnippets&quot;,&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Group Securities&quot;,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;Cluster Snippet Plugin&quot;,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://api.sonelli.com/images/plugins/com.groupsecs.juicesshclustersnippets.png&quot;,&quot;opensource&quot;:&quot;false&quot;,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;Run snippets on multiple connections faster and simpler.&quot;,&quot;repository&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;email&quot;:&quot;developer@groupsecs.com&quot;,&quot;url&quot;:&quot;https://www.groupsecs.com/clustersnippets/&quot;},{&quot;package&quot;:&quot;com.sonelli.juicessh.tasker&quot;,&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Sonelli Ltd&quot;,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;Tasker Plugin&quot;,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://api.sonelli.com/images/plugins/com.sonelli.juicessh.tasker.png&quot;,&quot;opensource&quot;:false,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;Automate your JuiceSSH sessions with this plugin for Tasker. Launch sessions, run commands/scripts and toggle port forwards from your Tasker profiles.&quot;,&quot;repository&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;email&quot;:&quot;support@sonelli.com&quot;,&quot;url&quot;:&quot;http://juicessh.com&quot;},{&quot;package&quot;:&quot;com.sonelli.portknocker&quot;,&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Sonelli Ltd&quot;,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;Port Knocker&quot;,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://api.sonelli.com/images/plugins/com.sonelli.portknocker.png&quot;,&quot;opensource&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;Port knocking allows you to only expose your SSH port if a certain set of TCP/UDP packets are received by the server. This plugin allows you to automatically craft and send those packets, then launch a JuiceSSH session.&quot;,&quot;repository&quot;:&quot;https://github.com/Sonelli/juicessh-portknocker&quot;,&quot;email&quot;:&quot;support@sonelli.com&quot;,&quot;url&quot;:&quot;http://juicessh.com&quot;},{&quot;package&quot;:&quot;com.sonelli.juicessh.auditlog&quot;,&quot;author&quot;:&quot;Sonelli Ltd&quot;,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;Plugin Audit Log&quot;,&quot;icon&quot;:&quot;https://api.sonelli.com/images/plugins/com.sonelli.juicessh.auditlog.png&quot;,&quot;opensource&quot;:true,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;View the last 7 days of plugin activity. See which plugins have launched JuiceSSH sessions and the commands they have run.&quot;,&quot;repository&quot;:&quot;https://github.com/Sonelli/juicessh-pluginaudit&quot;,&quot;email&quot;:&quot;support@sonelli.com&quot;,&quot;url&quot;:&quot;http://juicessh.com&quot;}]</string>
    <string name="account">New User</string>
    <int name="bash:version" value="116" />
</map>
